seotrickz.wordpress.com 2010-12-30

# Privacy Policy – Accessories-ATV Resource Directory

###  TRUCKS 

###  Utility ATV 

**Privacy Statement of Accessories ATV**

We are committed to protecting your privacy. The privacy, confidence, and trust of individuals who visit our website is important to us. No personal information is collected at this site unless provided voluntarily by an individual while participating in an activity that asks for the information.

**Cookies** "Cookies" are small piece of data that is sent to your Internet browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can't read data off of your computer hard disk or read cookie files created by other websites. Cookies do not damage your system. They are used to keep track of and store information so the user does not have to supply the information multiple times. The information that is collected through cookies at this site is handled in the same manner as other information collected here. You can configure your web browser to refuse cookies or to notify you when a web site attempts to send you a cookie. You can also check your hard drive for cookie files and delete them from your computer.

**Links to Other Sites** This website contains links to many other websites. These include links to websites operated by other government agencies, nonprofit organizations, and private businesses. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these sites and suggest you review their privacy statements.

**NOTIFICATION and CHANGES** Any modifications to our privacy practices will be reflected here. If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page so our users are aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under which circumstances, if any, we disclose it. Users should check this policy frequently to keep abreast of any changes. 

Permissions to Link or Post Permission is granted for linking to our site, individual pages or articles within the site. **

[**4ft double bed**](http://www.memoryfoammattresszleeps.co.uk/4ft-double-bed-special-offer.html)Memory foam is a fantastic new sleeping material, at Zleeps we have become more efficient at making memory foam and have made it our duty to drive the costs down.

**

 **

* [ ****](http://www.usedhandicapvans.net/sell-used-wheelchair-vans-we-buy-used-handicapped-vehicles.php)**[Vehicle Tracking](http://www.thinktracking.co.uk/)Think Tracking, a leading name in providing Vehicle tracking systems, GPS Tracking, Vehicle Tracking Devices, Vehicle Tracking UK. Our vehicle trackers are ideal for fleet tracking up to 1000 vehicles, and have been developed for cars, vans and HGVs. At Think Tracking we can find the perfect vehicle tracking solutions to suit any criteria.**  
**[Logistics Broker](http://byexpress.com/main/index.php?page=logistics)** We are specialist in providing world class logistics broker and logistics provider services at affordable prices to our customers.  
**[cheap moving boxes](http://www.removalboxes.co.uk/)** Packing supplies including removal & storage boxes. We deliver nationally to make things easy!  
Copyright © 2009 - Accessories ATV. All Rights Reserved. 
**
